examresultbd.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy! | Examresultbd

[](http://examresultbd.com/copyright-policy/copyright/)Policy

Privacy

At [examresultbd.com](http://examresultbd.com/) , the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us (See [this article](http://www.wp-insert.smartlogix.co.in/what-is-a-privacy-policy/) to learn more about Privacy Policies.)

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Bangladesh Jobs and Result collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the http://examresultbd.com/ website. This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by [Examresultbd.](http://examresultbd.com/)

**We respect your or user privacy! Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions, please don’t hesitate to let us know.**

**Resale or disclosure of information to third parties:**

**[Examresultbd](http://examresultbd.com/) does not sell, rent, loan or lease any personal information collected at our site or email lists.**

**Browser information collected on the website:**

**[Examresultbd](http://examresultbd.com/) analyzes our website logs to constantly improve the value of the materials available on website. Our website logs are not personally identifiable, and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site.**

**Use of cookies:**

**In order to improve browsing experience, we use cookies for redirection to concerned region.**

**[Examresultbd](http://examresultbd.com/) maintains several email lists to keep our members informed about breaking events. We do not sell, rent, loan or lease the addresses on our list to anyone.  
**

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, [examresultbd.com](http://examresultbd.com/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Feel Free to Ask...........

Comments
